But, sure, calcium sulfate could work.
(Sheldon:)Let's think out of the box for a moment.
(Sheldon:)How about a molecular sieve?
HOWARD & LEONARD:
Oh.
(Penny:)I've got a spaghetti strainer
in the kitchen.
(Sheldon:)Wow.
(Leonard:)Hey, we could liberate some
microporous charcoal from the chem lab.
(Penny:)Oh, great.
Raj, why don't you go get the charcoal?
Leonard, start working
on some preliminary website designs.
I'll make space in our apartment so we
can move the manufacturing process.
- Well, what's wrong with my apartment?
- It's not my apartment.
Wait, wait, what am I gonna do?
(Leonard:)Hey, it's your business.
Do whatever you want.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Penny:)Okay. Cool.
I'm gonna take a nap.
(Leonard:)I'm still tweaking things a little bit, but this
will give the general idea of the website.